[{"question":"which object is smaller?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The metal cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The plastic cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"What is the material of the large cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"Brick"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"Redunknown"}],"answer":0},{"question":"How many cubes there?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"4"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object has lower density?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small plastic cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large metal cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Is the small plastic cube heavier than the large metal cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has larger friction?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large metal cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small plastic cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has lower restitution?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small plastic cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large brick cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which quadrant will the large brick cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which quadrant will the small plastic cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object will stop moving earlier?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large brick cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small plastic cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object will stop moving first?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large metal cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large brick cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the large brick cube travel to quadrant \u2161?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will there a collision in the quadrant \u2163?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"How many collisions will happen between objects?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"<=3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":">3"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the large brick cube collide more than once?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the large brick cube collide with the wall in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the large brick cube collide with the small plastic cube in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which objects is the first collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The wall and the large metal cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large brick cube and the wall"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The large brick cube and the large metal cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The small plastic cube and the large metal cube"}],"answer":3},{"question":"Which objects is the last collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small plastic cube and the large brick cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The wall and the large brick cube"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The small plastic cube and the wall"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The wall and the large metal cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the large brick cube collide with other objects after it stops moving?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0}]